export const cards = [
    { question: "⭐💵", answer: "Starbucks" },
    { question: "💘✉️", answer: "Love Letter" },
    { question: "🌎☕", answer: "World Cup" },
    { question: "🧑🏻‍🦱📖", answer: "Facebook" },
    { question: "🕷️🚶🏻", answer: "Spider-Man" },
    { question: "👻🏠", answer: "Haunted House" },
    { question: "🦁👑", answer: "The Lion King" },
    { question: "🌧️🐱🐶", answer: "Raining Cats and Dogs" },
    { question: "🐝➡️🔙", answer: "Be Right Back" },
    { question: "😡⛽🚗 ", answer: "Madagascar" }
  ];
  